Please download the basic pants version from the library and add the virtual model to the scene from the femalev2 file editor.
Select the internal multidirectional line tool and create an internal line on the pants.
After selecting the internal line, you can copy and paste it.
When pasting, press the mouse button and right-click to set the number of lines that are adjacent to the internal line in the spring.
Select all the internal lines on the middle panel and select the line to be aligned with the panel line in the right-click menu.
Quickly click all the internal lines on the middle panel four times.
Cut the panel line prepared for folding.
Click the panel line prepared for folding.
Press the Shift key to move the panel in the horizontal direction.
Select the panel after cutting.
Select the panel after cutting, Ctrl-C and Ctrl-R to paste.
The pasted panels are not linked.
Therefore, we need to select the corresponding panels and apply the parallel panel panel and sewing line for them.
Select the panel line.
In the right-click menu, we can select the parallel panel.
After piecing all
the refer Kenny onto the panel line, use the mycket tool to paste the planer.
Attach the plate to the 3D window.
Stick thePE panel to the 3D window with a tool named Ladder setting.
After peaking the panel out 720 cm by English.
Since you've been monster when you can attach it, you can try or distress.
Add the inner line to the part of the fold-down straight line point
In the tool bar, select the fold-down fold-down
Click on the left side of the inner line
Move the mouse through all the inner lines
Then double click
In the spring, you can fold the inner line to the fold-down angle
The effect of the fold-down angle will be more obvious after hardening
When you fold the inner line and press it, the inner line will hit the center of the fold-down
Use the free sewing tool to fold the inner line
When sewing, you should place the straight line point as the center
Sew both sides
Ensure that the direction of the sewing line is consistent with the 3D window
Because the size of the pants is too small, the pleats are stretched
You can widen the pants by moving the outer line of the side seam and the hem of the pattern
Use the edit curve point tool to move the curve point to make it smoother
Next, we are going to make the waistband
Select the rectangle tool and press the button in the 2D window, you can enter the size of the pattern in the pop-up window
Ctrl D to align the pattern with the sewing line
Show arrangement point, click to arrange the waistband pattern around the virtual model
In the property editor, you can change the arrangement position
The waistband needs to be curved to better fit the curve of the virtual model
Use the edit curve point tool to add a curve point to make it smoother
Make sure the waistband pattern is square
Otherwise, there will be a corner in the sewing part
Freeze the waistband and fix the pattern in the 3D window
Use the free sewing tool to sew the pattern together, but please skip the part that has been sewn when sewing
Delete excess straight lines
You can move the pattern to adjust the width of the pants
Then you can adjust the length in along the waist
You can correct what you're doing
You can do it to your style
You can make the two curves leaning on top of each other
You can cooking the hook
In order to Вы清楚
In order to bottom the single type
design
Done
Vo Gym
Ctrl-D to create a symmetrical belt
You can select free sewing in the tool bar in the 3D window
The sewing tools selected in the 3D window can be used in the 2D window and 3D window at the same time
You can use the editing sewing line tool to move the sewing line
Reduce the particle diameter and increase the grid surface number to get more details
There is a bulge in the position where the belt and pants are sewn
You can use the adjustment straight line to shorten the bulge in the plate
In the material folder in the tool bar, select the cotton setting to apply to the current fabric
Remove the inner line and simulate the cut and cut will be more natural
This is a cute picture of the front and back of the side of the main bra by each other
Thank you.